# **MAKSYM TSYBULSKYI**

Sacramento, CA 95842 · 916-578-86-78 tomahawksmail@gmail · LinkedIn Profile · GitHub · WebSite

#### SUMMARY

I am an engineer with over 15 years of experience in IT. In total more than 12 years held the position of head of the IT department. My main qualities are self-management, responsibility and time-management. I always try to work for the result. I have completed a DevOps engineering course and I want to find a new job. I am always happy to learn something new and share my knowledge among my colleagues.

#### SKILLS

- Linux: Ubuntu, Debian, Amazon Linux

- MS Windows Server: AD, DNS, GPO, SMB

- Networking: Subnetting, TCP, UDP, HTTP(S), VPN

- laaC: Terraform

- SQL: MySQL (MariaDB), MS SQL Server

- Scripts: Python3, Bash - Version Control: Git, GitHub

- Containers: Docker, Docker Compose

- Clouds: AWS, Vodafone - CI/CD: Jenkins, Git Lab, GitHub

- Web server: NGINX

- Orchestration: Kubernetes, Docker Swarm - Observability: Logging with ELK Stack

- WSGI: Gunicorn+Flask

- Synchronization: Rsync

- Virtualization: VMware, Oracle Virtual Box, Vagrant

- Configuration Management: Ansible

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **02/2023 – CURRENT TIME**

#### INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST

MAGMA LINE INC · FULL-TIME

**USA, SACRAMENTO** 

CLINIC OF SAINT CATHERINE · FULL-TIME

UKRAINE, ODESA

- Maintenance, management and adaptation e-commerce website
- Maintenance IT infrastructure
- Maintenance WEB server

## 12/2012 - 03/2022

#### **HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT/ ARCHITECT**

- Created the entire infrastructure of the company (purchase and configuration of equipment)
- Prepared and partial transfer of services to the Cloud (AWS and Vodafone)
- Automation and optimization of processes using Python
- Maintened and backup of multiple databases (MySQL and MS SQL Server)
- Maintain Kubernetes Clusters with own internal web services

#### 05/2010 - 10/2012

#### **HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT**

"VIRTUS" · FULL-TIME UKRAINE, ODESA

- Construction and maintenance of IT infrastructure of the enterprise
- Maintened and backup of multiple databases
- Created two websites for the company

## 01/2006 - 06/2010

#### **CHIEF ENGINEER**

#### **SECURITY SYSTEMS INTEGRATOR**

"AGENT-SB" · FULL-TIME

UKRAINE, ODESA

- Design and installation of security systems
- Created the entire infrastructure of the company

## **EDUCATION**

### 2000 - 2006

## **ODESSA NATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS**

**ACADEMY BY O.S.POPOV** 

UKRAINE, ODESA

Bachelor's Degree in Telecommunications, Information Communication Networks

## COURSES & CERTIFICATES

02/2022 HILLEL IT school DevOps

01/2023 AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

01/2022 TP-LINK CERTIFIED PARTNER

01/2023 Troubleshooting: Amazon API Gateway

07/2022 AWS Compute Services Overview

01/2023 AWS Networking Basics 12/2021 AWS TECHNICAL ESSENTIALS 01/2023 AWS Networking Basics

01/2023 AWS Network Monitoring and Troubleshooting

Dear Hiring Manager!

Thank you for taking the time for this page.

I am a computer engineer with over 15 years of experience in IT. In total, I held the position of head of the IT department at CLINIC OF SAINT CATHERINE and "VIRTUS" for over 13 years.

I have extensive experience in the IT infrastructure of the businesses, and I constantly update my theoretical knowledge. I also know from experience what it means to manage and work with a team.

Therefore, I am confident that I can contribute to a cutting edge company like yours, focusing on results and great attention to detail. I possess the ability to learn quickly, often in difficult situations and to fully understand a new product or platform. I have excellent problem solving and problem solving skills, creating Automation, developing all kind of Cloud solutions with IaaC.

My best qualities are self-management, responsibility, integrity and timemanagement. I always work hard for good outcomes. I have already completed a DevOps engineering course and I am always happy to learn something new and share my knowledge among my colleagues.

Bachelor's Degree in Telecommunications, Information Communication Networks by Odessa National Academy of Telecommunications (Odesa, UKRAINE).

I am currently in Sacramento and am not yet ready to relocate. I have a U.S. work authorization permit.

I look forward to discussing my candidacy and suitability for this position during an interview in the near future. Thank you for giving me your time and attention.

Sincerely, Maksym Tsybulskyi